Everybody who's been wondering where
I've been the last few days, you see it
here. Have I been alive, George?
>> He's been alive.
>> What have I been doing?
>> Life lessons.
>> Working on cars all day long and going
through probably the hardest time of my
life.
You got to remember that content
creators are still normal people. We
still have broken down cars. We still
have personal lives. We still have
family problems. We still have real
world
And I feel like this is the biggest test
of my life.
A lot of things are coming up against me
ever since I started with those old
Bibles, man, and
this is a test and I'm going through it
right now.
If you're a praying person, please pray
for me. If you're a loving person,
please send me love. If you're a helping
person, please help me. Please help
George. I need all the help I can get
right now.
I think I've inspired a whole lot of
people over the years and I hope to keep
doing so, but right now I am slogging
through the shittiest sandwich you've
ever seen. Like for real.
Thank God I have a little help from my
friends.
>> I do this for a living, so it's not so
bad.